Guide to the George Mason University Office of the President records, 1949-2004
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: George W. Johnson, 1957-2004, (78 boxes)
  - Czarda, Larry: Arena management proposals [2 of 2], 1982-1990 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Czarda, Larry: Art in public places contracts, 1986-1990 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Czarda, Larry: Business services, monthly staff meetings, 1985-1988 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Czarda, Larry: Capital centre, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Czarda, Larry: Computer-aided acquisition and logistics systems (CALS) shared resource center, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Czarda, Larry: Computer-aided acquisition and logistics systems (CALS) shared resource center file, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Czarda, Larry: Correspondence (general), 1985-1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Czarda, Larry: Debbie Williams, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Czarda, Larry: Decentralization final reports committees, 1987-1992 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Czarda, Larry: Administrative decentralization in higher education by Donald J. Finley, March 21, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Czarda, Larry: Decentralization in higher education (general), 1988 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Czarda, Larry: Decentralization report, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Czarda, Larry: Decentralization Steering committee, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Czarda, Larry: Decentralization task force [1 of 2], 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Czarda, Larry: Decentralization task force [2 of 2], 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Czarda, Larry: Decentralization task force, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Czarda, Larry: Facility management group, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Czarda, Larry: General, 1984-1988 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Czarda, Larry: Government 241 introduction to public administration, 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Czarda, Larry: Higher education bond referendum, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Czarda, Larry: International Association of Auditorium Managers (IAAM) meeting, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Czarda, Larry: Organizational charts, 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Czarda, Larry: Parris, Robertson project, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center administrative coordination meeting, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center advisory group, 1985-1993 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center agreement for management, circa 1988 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center contracts [1 of 4], 1985-1991 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center contracts [2 of 4], 1985-1990 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center contracts [3 of 4], 1985-1991 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center contracts [4 of 4], 1985 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center event authorization forms, undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center management meetings, 1989, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center management update, 1989-1991 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center marketing, 1989-1992 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center monthly meetings, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center policy meetings, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center policy on religious and political events, 1991-1992 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center use, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Czarda, Larry: Patriot Center workfile, 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Czarda, Larry: Project Streamline [1 of 2], 1992 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Czarda, Larry: Project Streamline [2of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Czarda, Larry: Sherrens, 1985-1988 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Czarda, Larry: Sherrens, 1985-1992 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Czarda, Larry: Sherrens, staff meetings, 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Czarda, Larry: Spectacor, 1981-1985 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Czarda, Larry: Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Decentralization, 1992-1994 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Department for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Department of Transportation, 1991-1998 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Department of Education, 1991-1999 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Department of Employee Relations, 1994-1997 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Department of General Services, Division of Engineering and Buildings, 1990-1995 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Department of Health, 1991-1992 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Department of Housing and Community Development, 1987-1998 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Department of Information Technology, 1990-1997 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Department of Labor compliance review, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Department of Labor and Industry, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Department of Military Affairs, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Department of Mines, Minerals, and Energy, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Department of Minority Business Enterprise, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Department of Personnel and Training, 1992-1998 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Department of Planning and Budget [1 of 2], 1994-1995 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Department of Planning and Budget [2 of 2], 1992-1998 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Department of State Internal Auditor, 1991-1994 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Department of the State Police, 1990-1995 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Department of Taxation, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Department of the Treasury, 1990-1992 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Department of Waste Management, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Development strategy, 1989-1990 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Division of legislative automated systems, 1992-1997 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - The drive for greatness, circa 1980s (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Drug and alcohol survey final report, Fall 1987 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Dulles-Washington corridor, December 1990 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Economic bridges I and responsible use of computing, circa 1990, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Economic development: University of Massachusetts (UMASS) as a resource for economic change, December 1994 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Economic future of Commonwealth [1 of 2], 1995 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Economic future of Commonwealth [2 of 2], 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - ETD (Education Technology Development) pilot program, circa 1980s (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Employee of the month, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Employee of the month, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Employee of the month, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Employee of the month, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Employee relations committee, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - English Language Institute, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Entrepreneurial Center, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Equal opportunity, 1979-1980 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Equity office, affirmative action plan, 1990-1994 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Executive committee retreat, March 18-19, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - External relations task force report, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Facilities: Braddock Road, 1993-1995 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Facilities: Construction, 1990-1992 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Facilities: Motor pool, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Facilities: Patriot Center, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Facilities: Renovation projects, 1992, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Facilities: Space, 1990-1993 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Facilities Planning: Student Union, phase II, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Faculty salaries, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Faculty senate, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Faculty senate, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Faculty senate, 1992 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Faculty senate, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Faculty senate, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Faculty task force, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Fairfax, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Fairfax County parkway, 1984-1988 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Fairfax County Schools Blue Ribbon Commission, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Federal Theatre Project, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Federal Theatre Project, transfer to Library of Congress correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Field House access road, 1979-1984 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Field House applications for approval of working drawings and specifications, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Field House purchase orders, 1980-1984 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Field House Washington Testing Inc., 1979 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Financial aid, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Financial aid, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Financial aid, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Financial aid, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Financial aid, 1993-1996 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Fulbright fellowship, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Funds for Excellence correspondence, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Funds for Excellence early identification program, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Funds for Excellence early identification program, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Funds for Excellence policy and procedure (draft), 1979 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Funds for Excellence proposal, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Funds for Excellence proposal, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Funds for Excellence proposal, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Funds for Excellence proposal, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Funds for Excellence proposal, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Funds for Excellence science and mathematics proposal, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - George Mason Day, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - George Mason medal recipient commencement remarks by Joanne Johnson, May 18, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - George Mason Press "Scorpion of the Sea" correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - George Mason sculpture by Wendy Ross, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - George Mason stamp, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - George Mason stamp, May 7, 1981 (Box 132)
  - Governor's files: Advisory to the media, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Governor's files: Agencies with society of education, March 21, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Governor's files: Center for Innovative Technology (CIT) board of directors meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Governor's files: Center for Innovative Technology (CIT) budget, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Governor's files: Commission on Government Reform, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Governor's files: Commission on Government Reform, Blue Ribbon strike force [1 of 2], 1994 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Governor's files: Commission on Government Reform, Blue Ribbon strike force [1 of 2], 1994 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Governor's files: Commission on Government Reform customer relations, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Governor's files: Commission on Restructuring, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Governor's files: Consolidated salary authorization for faculty positions in institutions of higher education, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Governor's files: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Governor's files: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Governor's files: Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Governor's files: Crime bill, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Governor's files: Department of planning and budget, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Governor's files: Dulles airport regional economic study commission, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Governor's files: Entrepreneurship center, 1991-1993 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Governor's files: Executive memorandum and orders, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Governor's files: General, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Governor's files: Global market studies, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Governor's files: Fellows program, 1991-1996 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Governor's files: Grants referral program, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Governor's files: Guidelines and eligibility for in-state tuition, circa 1994-1996 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Governor's files: Higher education restructuring plan, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Governor's files: Interactive management, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Governor's files: Legislative proposals, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Governor's files: Regional economic development advisory council, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Governor's files: Report of secretaries of administration and finance, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Governor's files: Report of the VCCS infrastructure task force, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Governor's files: Reports Salmon, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Governor's files: Savings bond campaign, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Governor's files: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Governor's files: Secretary of education correspondence, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Governor's files: Service employees, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Governor's files: Special education programs, 1981, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Governor's files: Governor speeches, 1977-1995 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Governor's files: Utility audit, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Governor's files: Virginia desegregation plan for 1987, 1987-1992 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Governor's task force on substance abuse and sexual assault, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Governor's task force on substance abuse and sexual assault, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Governor's task force on substance abuse and sexual assault, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Governor's task force on substance abuse and sexual assault, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Governor's task force on substance abuse and sexual assault, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Governor's task force on substance abuse and sexual assault, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Graduate advisory committee (Visit, report, and related correspondence), October 1973 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Greek life task force report, February 2, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Guest book for corporate art show, 1980, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Guest book from Mathy House, 1983-1988 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Guidelines for classified employee, time and attendence, June 5, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Guidelines on life-threatening illness, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Harry S. Truman scholarship foundation, 1983-1990 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Highlights of GMU history, 1957-1979 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Hirst lecture series, 1980-1991 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Inaugural: Biographical sketch of George W. Johnson, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Inaugural: Board of Visitors inaugural resolution (photocopy), 1979 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Inaugural: Check list, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Inaugural: Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Inaugural: Invitation (copy) to inaugural ball, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Inaugural: Itinerary for President and Mrs. Johnson, April 6, 1979-July 1979 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Inaugural: George W. Johnson's inaugural speech, April 7, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Inauguration: Guest list (invitations, replies, tickets), 1979 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Inauguration: Gunston Hall dinner pre-inauguration, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Inauguration: List of all marching in inauguration procession, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Inauguration: Month calendar, April 1979 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Inauguration: Newsclippings, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Inauguration: Photograph of George W. Johnson, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Inauguration: Program, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Inauguration: Purchase orders, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Inauguration: Reel-to-reel audiotape, April 7, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Inauguration: Rehearsal, cleanup, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Inauguration: Seating, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Information systems and hardware review audit, April 24, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Inter-institutional articulation committee, 1991-1994 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Institutional membership, 1985-1994 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - International relations, trips to Spain, Taiwan, 1988-1990 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Invitation, April 5, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Invitation logs [1 of 2], 1985-1990 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Invitation logs [2 of 2], 1990-1996 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Invitations and cards, 1980s-1990s (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Johnson Center dedication program, April 12, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Kazin, Alfred, 1989-1990 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Krasnow Institute for advanced study, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Law School, 1980s (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Law School: Advisory committee, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Law School: Agreement contract, 1978-1983 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) accreditation, 1979-1980 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) accreditation, 1979-1980 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) accreditation, 1981, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) accreditation, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) accreditation, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) accreditation, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) accreditation, 1989-1990 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) accreditation, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Law School: ABA (American Bar Association) standards, 1986-1989 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Law School: Annual reports, 1991-1994 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Law School: Approval of law schools procedures, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Law School: Board of Directors, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Law School: Budget, 1978-1987 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Law School: Catalog, 1976-1992 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Law School: Conveyance, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Law School: Dean's reports, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Law School: Dean's reports, January 14, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Law School: Dedication, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Law School: Dedication, August 23, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Law School: Faculty bylaws, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Law School: Feasibility study, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Law School: Graduation, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Law School: Graduation celebration, August 23, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Law School: History, 1973-1976 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Law School: History, "History of the School of Law", 1993 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Law School: IGI findings report, 1975 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Law School: Inspection team report, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Law School: Letters of support, 1978-1980 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Law School: Merger, 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Law School: Miscellaneous, 1979-1984 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Law School: Newsletters, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Law School: Newspaper clippings, 1974-1995 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Law School: Quarterly memos, 1988-1992 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Law School: Self-study, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Law School: Self-study, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Law School: Self-study, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Law School: Self-study, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Law School: Senate Bill no. 87, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Law School: "The Special Skills of Advocacy", 1974 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Law School: Statement of purpose, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Law School: Study of legal education and manpower, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Lawsuits: Margaret Dear vs. GMU, 1991-1992 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Learning initiatives project, 1991-1992 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Legal affairs GMU, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Library GMU, 1990-1999 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Library program goals, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Mason Scholar committee handbook, 1990s (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Mason Scholar: The George Mason report, July 1988 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Mason Scholars, 1990-1997 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - The Mellon Foundation, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Memorandum: Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Memorandum: Results of payroll questionnaire, June 19, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - The Metro-Dulles consortium, January 1991 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Miller, Helen Hill, April 20, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Minnick, John B.: "Reseperation of powers", 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous notes and papers, 1991-1993 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous presidential papers, 1986-1989 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Mobil oil "Desert storm" scholarship, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - National alumni forum, 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - NCAA compliance task force, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Newsclippings, 1983-1998 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Newsclippings, 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper articles on George W. Johnson's retirement, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Nomination sample letters, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Northern Virginia Community Foundation, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Office for Civil Rights, 1990-1995 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Office of the Attorney General, 1990-1997 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Office of the Attorney General, drug education program, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Office of the Attorney General, Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) inquiry (Nancy Finch), 1996 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Office of the Attorney General, Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) requests [1 of 2], 1995-1996 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Office of the Attorney General, Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) requests [2 of 2], 1996 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Office of the Attorney General lawsuits, 1987-1996 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Office of the Attorney General lawsuits, 1989-1996 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Outstanding faculty awards, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Parking services: Parking report (Parking task force), November 1989 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Parking services: Parking finance task force report, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Parking services: Rules and regulations, 1990-1996 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Partnerships: Mount Vernon Woods Elementary School, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Partnerships: Washington Market, 1990-1993 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Patriot club, 1990-1996 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Patriot service corporation, February 7, 1996 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Peer harassment: Hassles for women on campus, September 1988 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Performance based pay committee, 1993-1994 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - The PEW roundtable, 1993-1995 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Photo album, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 132)
    Photographs of George Johnson, Jack Herrity, and other Fairfax and George Mason representatives in Taiwan.
  - Plan for Alternative General Education (PAGE), 1990 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Policy and planning site projects, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Preliminary information requested of apply institutions, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Program for 2004 Charter Day at William and Mary (Honorary degree awarded to George W. Johnson) (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Prince William Campus proposals posting, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Prince William College newspaper clippings, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Prince William County: Proposal for a University presence in PWC, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Prince William Institute, 1989-1991 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Prince William Institute budget, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Proposals to restructure teacher preparation grades NK-12, circa 1991 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Provost: Memorandum and correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Provost: Memorandum and correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Provost: Memorandum and correspondence, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Provost search committee, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Public-private housing task force, 1989-1990 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Recommendations of Governors Strike Force on Education, undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Registrar, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 8)